"Do you have Leonard's
email address?"
(Sheldon:)And...
"Never mind, I found it."
(Amy:)I can't believe
he picked you over me.
(Howard:)You don't want to read a paper
by some old has-been
(Howard:)who hasn't done
any real science in decades.
(Raj:)Yeah, it's nothing to cry about.
(Sheldon:)Sheldon Cooper does not cry.
(Howard:)It's true. You'd rust.
(Sheldon:)And to think I idolized that man.
(Sheldon:)And why?
(Sheldon:)At the end of the day he's just
another Hollywood phony.
(Amy:)Is it really worth
getting upset about?
(Sheldon:)They say don't meet your heroes.
(Sheldon:)Don't peek behind
that curtain of fame and celebrity,
(Sheldon:)because if you do,
(Sheldon:)degenerate carnival folk.
(Amy:)Come on,
he's a retired kids show host.
(Sheldon:)That's even worse.
Using the sweet candy of science
(Sheldon:)to trick children into loving him.